hitid,workerid,raw_json
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5d41ff88146fcc001a139150,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:00.353Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fan', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:08.007Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'february', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:11.751Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'feelings', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:16.406Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'freedom', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:19.103Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:20.751Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:22.623Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:24.431Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'funny', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:26.255Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fantastic', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:29.247Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'freak', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:38.807Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fam', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:45.007Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:49.767Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'farm', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:51.575Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'farming', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:53.247Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'Farmington', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:57.415Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '60', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:43.400Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'space'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'long'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'No strategy involved. It just came to me.', 'q7': 'none', 'sliderValue': '60'}, 'workerId': '5d41ff88146fcc001a139150', 'assignmentId': '66c537735ae86318175df4b4', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:48:17.182Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,668d822d705c807ed4664ae1,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:39:25.781Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:39:30.515Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Flight ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:39:34.153Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Frigid', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:39:38.436Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Fame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:39:41.770Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Famous', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:39:45.051Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Factual', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:39:48.398Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Fact', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:39:51.414Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Forgiven', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:39:55.177Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Forsake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:39:58.835Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Found ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:05.704Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Fright', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:09.572Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'Frightening', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:14.286Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'Freedom', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:19.487Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'Fax', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:23.577Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '68', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:40:45.612Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Spider'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Day'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Door'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Phone'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Not at all helpful', 'q6': 'Try to think what fit for all 3', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '23'}, 'workerId': '668d822d705c807ed4664ae1', 'assignmentId': '66c5372516f98496f96392f6', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:46:22.529Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6604487bcefa53a1ccd4a684,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:40:33.444Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:40.680Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fudge', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:52.933Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Fridge', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:57.170Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:00.612Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Funk', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:04.324Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Fund', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:16.688Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Fin', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:20.059Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:23.502Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Fine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:26.969Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'Fuse', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:32.317Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '71', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:23.743Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Bar'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Bank'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Long'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Coat'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'Finding an associated word for the first object and moving on from there. ', 'q7': 'I did not', 'sliderValue': '73'}, 'workerId': '6604487bcefa53a1ccd4a684', 'assignmentId': '66c537405ae86318175df4a5', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:48:06.932Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66c1310dc23f1e2109f166ce,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:37.104Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fried', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:40.196Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:41.433Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:44.122Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fire', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:45.425Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fret', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:48.514Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fred', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:49.415Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fry', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:51.519Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'foot', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:55.340Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'feet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:58.253Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'focus', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:03.213Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fuck', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:07.499Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fad', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:19.773Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'fabric', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:21.371Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'failure', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:22.810Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'far', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:26.587Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'fairy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:27.993Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'faith', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:31.459Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'false', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:33.358Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'fame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:34.586Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:36.213Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '50', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:59.202Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blue'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blood'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'brown'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'thinking', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '50'}, 'workerId': '66c1310dc23f1e2109f166ce', 'assignmentId': '66c5379246d161429bf005d8', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:48:34.704Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5ef00061e45c1f1988455df5,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:25.676Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'full', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:28.665Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:29.674Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:31.193Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'foot', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:32.952Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fool', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:34.697Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:38.601Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fume', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:40.889Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'funeral', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:44.681Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fruit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:45.720Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fig', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:46.890Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'figure', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:49.673Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:51.545Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'freedom', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:53.194Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'fan', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:58.393Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'feign', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:00.921Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'fat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:08.618Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'frat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:10.409Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'fraternity', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:13.560Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '34', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:43.245Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'mink'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'fool'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'twitter'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'income'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I went with the first word I thought of.', 'q7': 'No.', 'sliderValue': '20'}, 'workerId': '5ef00061e45c1f1988455df5', 'assignmentId': '66c537de59a9db2d390f3efc', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:48:39.980Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,665226461593afe79894c16c,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:22.255Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:28.919Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:31.816Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fossil', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:35.203Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fart', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:38.433Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'flake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:42.999Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:51.937Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'front', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:56.160Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'far', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:59.058Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'farther', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:03.300Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:08.455Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'frost', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:18.582Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'first', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:21.485Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '68', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:11.979Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'long'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'door'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'point'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'thinking of words', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '73'}, 'workerId': '665226461593afe79894c16c', 'assignmentId': '66c5377a61bfa3df3e12440d', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:48:47.763Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5e3f04fdb721da159417a725,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:40:58.404Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fun fall friend family forlorn folk four', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:47.074Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '55', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:59.517Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'coat'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spider'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '10': {'HideTime': 28.335}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'Just trying my hardest to put something before or after', 'q7': 'none', 'sliderValue': '55'}, 'workerId': '5e3f04fdb721da159417a725', 'assignmentId': '66c537524aa06668f7b5f966', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:48:48.124Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5ceef64577a506001714c032,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:25.959Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fool', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:37.021Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'first', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:41.303Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:43.611Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:45.900Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'flower', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:51.309Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'flatulent', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:03.703Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'figure', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:08.744Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'figurine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:12.688Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'first', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:16.914Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '58', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:09.804Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'coat'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'sore'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'hour'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Not at all helpful', 'q6': 'no strategy', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '56'}, 'workerId': '5ceef64577a506001714c032', 'assignmentId': '66c537865fd54e326a2c18f2', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:49:16.166Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5b2973a08c745200013b84ae,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:40.264Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'furniture', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:05.836Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'floor', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:14.058Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'freezer', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:24.173Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fridge', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:33.055Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '20', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:59.025Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'black'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'tried to find a wotd that linked the others', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '20'}, 'workerId': '5b2973a08c745200013b84ae', 'assignmentId': '66c5377990243da912682772', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:50:02.771Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66958688126ae60131512012,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:20.510Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:24.409Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:29.080Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fuck', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:33.288Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Funny', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:36.296Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Fishy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:38.616Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:42.359Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:56.470Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Fishing', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:12.708Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Fishing', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:16.468Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '34', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:42.862Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Spin'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Meat'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Light'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'teeth'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'None', 'q7': 'Nope', 'sliderValue': '37'}, 'workerId': '66958688126ae60131512012', 'assignmentId': '66c537d373fb365951198f50', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:49:24.727Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66b14d28b85cfe52279f0aa5,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:10.720Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:14.836Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Follow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:17.900Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Feed', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:18.956Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Feeder', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:20.316Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Felt', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:21.452Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Feelings', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:23.972Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Feather', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:25.412Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Feathers', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:27.652Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Feathered', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:30.292Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Fault', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:31.676Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Faults', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:33.516Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'Faulter', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:34.868Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'Fawn', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:36.412Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'Freedom', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:40.228Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'Facility', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:43.796Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'Faculty', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:46.252Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'Finance', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:47.780Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'Financial', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:50.004Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'Fellow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:52.284Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'Finite', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:54.564Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 20, 'name': 'Figure', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:58.148Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 21, 'name': 'Figures', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:00.836Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 22, 'name': 'Figured', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:02.780Z'}, {'id': 23, 'iid': 23, 'name': 'Freak', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:06.469Z'}, {'id': 24, 'iid': 24, 'name': 'Freaks', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:07.837Z'}, {'id': 25, 'iid': 25, 'name': 'Freaked', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:09.333Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '85', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:50.822Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spider'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'beaver'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'Trying to think of something that included a trademark tail as well as fur. ', 'q7': 'The text cut off in the break game of snake. Nbd.', 'sliderValue': '85'}, 'workerId': '66b14d28b85cfe52279f0aa5', 'assignmentId': '66c537c6c23973f9258458e3', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:49:29.075Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,61508722f5076c1a0ea2062b,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:46.451Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:51.715Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fist', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:52.868Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:54.609Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fear', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:55.957Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fence', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:59.340Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'father', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:00.768Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fix', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:05.375Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fins', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:08.473Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:11.567Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:13.579Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fire', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:15.961Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:20.536Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'future', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:23.298Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'fruit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:29.016Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'French fry', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:34.214Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'ferret', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:38.782Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'feet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:43.044Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'few', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:44.376Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'fair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:46.334Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '70', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:04.950Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'length'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I just thought of a word that I associated with the first word and then checked if it worked for the other two words\n', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '70'}, 'workerId': '61508722f5076c1a0ea2062b', 'assignmentId': '66c5374304bbe257d0790a74', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:49:33.005Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,664538489509c0d5d5f25338,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:50.372Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'forget', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:55.524Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:57.779Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:59.067Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fester', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:01.299Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'forgotten', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:03.873Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'flacid', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:07.305Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fence', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:11.547Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fork', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:16.643Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fell', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:21.642Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fist', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:24.866Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fart', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:30.506Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:39.105Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:40.433Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'folks', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:42.338Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '32', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:33.529Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'coin'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '10': {'HideTime': 2.24}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I just thought of each word and thought of words associated with each word.', 'q7': 'No.', 'sliderValue': '34'}, 'workerId': '664538489509c0d5d5f25338', 'assignmentId': '66c537ba096f6cc0f1d676fb', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:49:53.801Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,65564ac4a40e1a913f825bba,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:46.699Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:54.280Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Friends', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:59.163Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:01.674Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Fiction', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:06.139Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Fortune', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:11.317Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Famine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:14.600Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Facts', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:17.943Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Fortnite', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:23.207Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Fork', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:25.245Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Fumble', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:29.836Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Fort', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:33.484Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'Funny', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:41.237Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'Fart', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:44.561Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '74', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:26.524Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Big'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'thinking through each word', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '67'}, 'workerId': '65564ac4a40e1a913f825bba', 'assignmentId': '66c537d675655b00c9c06264', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:50:12.273Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,63f7b3a6b0aa00ea41771348,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:40:25.100Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'factor', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:28.396Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'flee', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:29.610Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'flea', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:31.049Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:32.245Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:34.908Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:37.533Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'flare', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:39.487Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'four', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:41.518Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fear', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:44.235Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fare', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:45.555Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:47.140Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fore', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:51.125Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'flop', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:54.064Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'flap', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:40:57.501Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'flip', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:00.942Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'flipper', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:02.482Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'flapper', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:03.973Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'found', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:07.025Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'founder', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:14.028Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'flounder', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:16.240Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 20, 'name': 'final', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:19.133Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 21, 'name': 'finale', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:20.513Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 22, 'name': 'fin', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:23.125Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '66', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:31.194Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blood'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'hair'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'mainly just came up instinctively once the words popped up', 'q7': 'none', 'sliderValue': '70'}, 'workerId': '63f7b3a6b0aa00ea41771348', 'assignmentId': '66c537cfabf16acb2ccbe71d', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:47:52.952Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66c3d2cfe269ff14a61b48b6,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:58.007Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:04.578Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fudge', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:09.251Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'From', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:12.647Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Fart', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:15.774Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Forgo', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:21.063Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Forget', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:25.105Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:29.034Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Frozen', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:33.356Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Found', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:38.485Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Flown', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:42.487Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Faith', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:48.203Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'Fair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:51.772Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'Fawn', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:56.454Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:57.100Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '69', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:25.920Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Money'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Material'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Snow'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Head'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'Going through each word individually', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '58'}, 'workerId': '66c3d2cfe269ff14a61b48b6', 'assignmentId': '66c538181d176ab4440567e3', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:50:46.858Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,665616bd2e3c013cde5789f5,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:22.454Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fork', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:25.065Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'flock', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:27.145Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fart', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:30.360Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'far', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:31.280Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:32.656Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fare', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:34.136Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'flower', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:37.512Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'flounder', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:40.888Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'flow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:42.464Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fold', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:45.832Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'foster', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:49.168Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'forest', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:50.680Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'fort', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:52.623Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'fig', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:57.711Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'fog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:59.419Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'fern', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:06.351Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'fried', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:08.631Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'fry', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:10.135Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'fly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:12.771Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:17.015Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 20, 'name': 'funk', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:19.463Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '21', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:36.310Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'wash'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I tried to come up with any associations i could but I found myself missing the AI help, I kind of panicked and did the best I could ', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '10'}, 'workerId': '665616bd2e3c013cde5789f5', 'assignmentId': '66c537addbbcd5b57412f05f', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:50:47.951Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5dacdf401e90f600132de0e6,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:31.234Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'frog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:34.679Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:36.993Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:40.100Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'facade', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:42.605Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'feign', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:45.648Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'feint', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:47.954Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'faint', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:49.224Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'flay', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:53.263Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fry', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:57.053Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'feed', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:05.635Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fetter', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:08.852Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'foot', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:12.618Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'follow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:17.785Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:19.892Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'freeze', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:25.031Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'full', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:29.482Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '30', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:09.148Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blue'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '10': {'HideTime': 25.726000000000003}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': ""I didn't really have a strategy, just knew it would most likely be a prefix. I play a daily puzzle finding connections between words so it was more intuition than strategy."", 'q7': 'None', 'sliderValue': '28'}, 'workerId': '5dacdf401e90f600132de0e6', 'assignmentId': '66c537f85cde01398191bc44', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:50:53.727Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66639d063066dd36d7ac5a1b,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:42.241Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'for', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:49.355Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fact', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:53.060Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'forest', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:57.951Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Forest', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:02.611Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'facts', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:06.599Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'factual', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:11.008Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'famous', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:14.805Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:17.830Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fetch', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:30.397Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'feast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:37.591Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '42', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:23.638Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'sea'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'scrap'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'face'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'cool'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'a little easy', 'q7': 'not really', 'sliderValue': '37'}, 'workerId': '66639d063066dd36d7ac5a1b', 'assignmentId': '66c5379aabf16acb2ccbe70f', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:02.098Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6266a888ce0c626836c91bc6,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:45.312Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fragrant', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:52.628Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:54.851Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'follow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:59.732Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:03.067Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fellow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:05.739Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:07.947Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fortune', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:11.251Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fortunate', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:15.403Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:17.843Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:20.635Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fill', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:26.910Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'file', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:29.398Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'flick', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:32.462Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'fiction', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:36.718Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'frame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:40.422Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'fry', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:43.238Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '77', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:59.084Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blood'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': ""I just looked at each word and came up with a combined word and then went to the next two to see if that word applied. If it didn't I would start again."", 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '81'}, 'workerId': '6266a888ce0c626836c91bc6', 'assignmentId': '66c537d7e279031a8ffbcac6', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:03.848Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,65df3cf4bf05d8eff24ed78b,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:06.800Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:10.580Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:11.740Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:13.146Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:15.159Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'forego', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:17.297Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'future', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:21.205Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'first', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:24.253Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:27.041Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'flake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:29.457Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fender', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:33.271Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:47.020Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:54.261Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'fist', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:05.353Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '20', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:35.563Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spider'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'line'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I picked one of the words and went through the list of associated words with that single word. Then I compared those words to see if they also fit with the other two.', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '16'}, 'workerId': '65df3cf4bf05d8eff24ed78b', 'assignmentId': '66c5380a680630617fb784c7', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:08.608Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,63c0e1b1ee5ca75f61e3b2e1,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:19.045Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '64', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:51.774Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spider'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '10': {'HideTime': 287.364}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I thought about what they have in common', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '64'}, 'workerId': '63c0e1b1ee5ca75f61e3b2e1', 'assignmentId': '66c5378081764bb22d62ad03', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:10.243Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5ffe3f18adbaca4ddb7e4006,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:42.736Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fork', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:52.612Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'final', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:59.595Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:09.035Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'forest', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:12.475Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fairy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:17.851Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fix', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:21.915Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:23.755Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'far', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:25.403Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'from', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:30.635Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:30.771Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fidget', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:35.227Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:39.635Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '25', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:12.170Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'day'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blue'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '10': {'HideTime': 5.207}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'saying them out loud to find the connection.', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '28'}, 'workerId': '5ffe3f18adbaca4ddb7e4006', 'assignmentId': '66c537a555125f766d5feab5', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:10.465Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,60572e792b7a4cff55a2ad57,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:40:57.791Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fish, Frog, Fillet, Faker, Font, Fantastic, Freak, Frolick, Feather, Feet, Flap, Fret ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:43.819Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '64', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:34.615Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'fools'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'storm'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I tried to think of word associations but I also tried to think about actually using words that connected them - so I thought about words that sounded similar to a connecting word - I understand now that I may not have made sense, but I suspect you, the producers of this task would make it the entire point, with the AI giving us words that had familiar word associations between the three words, and with the no AI help having words that it was difficult to find a single word connection with - meaning the AI was a red herring tool', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '29'}, 'workerId': '60572e792b7a4cff55a2ad57', 'assignmentId': '66c53758891ec2c34fcf7441', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:11.672Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,63b753401eb907a465852f01,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:57.140Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:01.211Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fran', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:05.339Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:07.363Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Frame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:09.819Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Frog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:12.251Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Feeble', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:16.627Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Feasible', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:21.851Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Forward', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:24.139Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '59', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:18.054Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Snow'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'arm'}, '10': {'HideTime': 133.234}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I used some of what I saw in practice rounds', 'q7': 'Nope, thank you!', 'sliderValue': '60'}, 'workerId': '63b753401eb907a465852f01', 'assignmentId': '66c5382e2e14766e5d721785', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:14.037Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5832fa8996ecce0001d65197,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:54.352Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:57.693Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fin', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:59.439Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:01.043Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'final', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:02.333Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'freak', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:04.164Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fork', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:06.231Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fright', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:09.819Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'finish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:16.147Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fort', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:19.192Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'far', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:21.404Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'farm', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:22.913Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fear', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:28.646Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:35.722Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:37.591Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'fudge', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:46.657Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'front', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:49.764Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'file', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:53.260Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '37', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:39.749Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'foot'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Coat'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Bank'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I just looked at all three words and thought of phrases/other words that could be made from them.', 'q7': 'Everything worked during the task', 'sliderValue': '37'}, 'workerId': '5832fa8996ecce0001d65197', 'assignmentId': '66c53811cab47445a30d8bd0', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:15.782Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5733464fbc6923000fcd2de1,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:12.090Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:17.924Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'friendly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:19.453Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:20.665Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fry', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:22.021Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fried', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:22.979Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'french', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:24.600Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'freak', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:28.232Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'four', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:32.777Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fourth', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:34.279Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fourteen', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:37.279Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fourty', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:39.276Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'forty', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:41.225Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'foal', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:44.940Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'folk', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:46.996Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'female', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:49.503Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'feminine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:51.005Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:54.644Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'fallow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:56.361Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'fang', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:00.066Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'fade', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:03.571Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 20, 'name': 'faded', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:05.924Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 21, 'name': 'fare', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:08.149Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 22, 'name': 'flake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:10.072Z'}, {'id': 23, 'iid': 23, 'name': 'flaky', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:11.820Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '75', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:52.497Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blood'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'space'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'Just thinking of something they have in common', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '75'}, 'workerId': '5733464fbc6923000fcd2de1', 'assignmentId': '66c5383570eb9fe86fda0526', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:17.334Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5e09461913064422d0004ecf,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:50.247Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'frog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:54.044Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fracking', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:00.175Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'full', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:03.843Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'foliage', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:09.054Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:09.155Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:10.398Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fumble', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:13.114Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'feline', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:15.400Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'flex', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:16.691Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'flush', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:20.901Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'flame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:23.839Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'flushing', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:26.476Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'flaming', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:28.134Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'falling', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:30.078Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'fetal', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:32.644Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'front', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:37.428Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'frock', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:40.078Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'flew', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:45.082Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'flute', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:47.245Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '95', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:15.205Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'stole'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'black'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'door'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'Thinking of relationships and words in common.', 'q7': 'No.', 'sliderValue': '95'}, 'workerId': '5e09461913064422d0004ecf', 'assignmentId': '66c5386b589628dadee9753f', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:18.077Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,664cf32f550b719c453c77b3,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:00.233Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fruit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:03.908Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fork', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:05.774Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'flower', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:09.114Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'frantic', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:12.567Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fashion', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:17.315Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fable', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:19.480Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'flour', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:22.913Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'form', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:26.473Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'foreign', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:34.209Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fantasy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:40.489Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'feeling', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:46.828Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fever', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:49.879Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'fairy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:54.863Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'famous', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:58.922Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '55', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:02.824Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'big'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blue'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'shot'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I tried finding associated words for one word (screen) and seeing if any fit with the other two words.', 'q7': 'Nope!', 'sliderValue': '60'}, 'workerId': '664cf32f550b719c453c77b3', 'assignmentId': '66c537737f452896826cb46e', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:18.152Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,667ebc629093f022db34278f,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:07.095Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fire', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:09.835Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'feelings', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:11.825Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fertile', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:13.433Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'folks', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:15.247Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'folklore', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:17.428Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fairies', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:18.975Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fireman', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:23.820Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'flamethrower', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:26.695Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fart', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:34.886Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'flatulence', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:37.012Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'flick', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:38.118Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'flight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:43.718Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'float', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:44.914Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'fleet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:46.462Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'fair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:52.970Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:53.773Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'fancy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:55.755Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 20, 'name': 'farmer', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:57.250Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 21, 'name': 'flint', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:00.796Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 22, 'name': 'fireplace', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:03.805Z'}, {'id': 23, 'iid': 23, 'name': 'fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:06.440Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '65', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:13.270Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'cracked'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'animal'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'precious'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'lost'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': ""I found it quite difficult. I kept bouncing ideas around in my head but I wasn't able to think of one that included both stetch and hair/time."", 'q7': 'None', 'sliderValue': '30'}, 'workerId': '667ebc629093f022db34278f', 'assignmentId': '66c537c52662226dfb8708a2', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:27.353Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,63d8966cb1c8fda2f6006864,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:17.826Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Flop', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:22.102Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:24.790Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:26.687Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:31.494Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Fence', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:38.454Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Fool', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:44.518Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Felled', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:53.174Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Fed', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:55.990Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Forde', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:04.518Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Fast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:11.574Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'few', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:17.286Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '58', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:47.097Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spider'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'tree'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '10': {'HideTime': 6.729}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'Just brainstorming frantically and think of words that join with one of the terms, and then see if they link to the other two', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '52'}, 'workerId': '63d8966cb1c8fda2f6006864', 'assignmentId': '66c537b19d27b9f7fd449576', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:36.244Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,64077ddd11208afe2bec171a,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:58.708Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fruit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:04.602Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:06.545Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'feet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:07.905Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fear', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:10.689Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:13.377Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:15.025Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:18.801Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'for', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:22.881Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'full', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:24.817Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:28.897Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:31.873Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fire', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:33.057Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:49.394Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'fan', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:54.177Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'fat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:58.337Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '57', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:29.147Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blood'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': ""I didn't have much of a strategy I felt like I instantly knew the answer so I used my intuition."", 'q7': 'No.', 'sliderValue': '63'}, 'workerId': '64077ddd11208afe2bec171a', 'assignmentId': '66c53844269cc2a81d49918c', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:42.119Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5f6cdde7a8d71310b06e402a,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:00.079Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'finger', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:03.639Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:05.435Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fuck', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:08.567Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:10.755Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'feelings', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:13.478Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:15.415Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'frumpy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:18.413Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:21.754Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'figures', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:27.437Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'finnesse', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:33.746Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'folly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:38.148Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'flick', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:44.587Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'feed', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:49.308Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'fox', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:52.897Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'fort', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:58.512Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '57', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:20.112Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spider'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'door'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'hug'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'just trying to brainstorm', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '40'}, 'workerId': '5f6cdde7a8d71310b06e402a', 'assignmentId': '66c538548ad07882f845b0bf', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:49.809Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6674d66fb9e8304fd5bf10d1,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:12.822Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:19.673Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:22.742Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:28.167Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'first', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:29.813Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'focus', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:31.358Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fundamental', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:34.498Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'finger', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:37.895Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'foyer', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:40.747Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'for', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:42.472Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'field', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:46.960Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fierce', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:49.910Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:53.749Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'feed', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:03.775Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'fork', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:09.032Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '20', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:12.640Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Door'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'sound it out and think', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '24'}, 'workerId': '6674d66fb9e8304fd5bf10d1', 'assignmentId': '66c53838c0d28061a34558b3', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:52.192Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,613f1ff71f92991679f72614,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:56.850Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '100', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:03.243Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'Snow/phone/pine'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Copy/black/fly'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Bait/spine/monitor'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Frame'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'No strategy, I thouht of words that can go with the three', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '50'}, 'workerId': '613f1ff71f92991679f72614', 'assignmentId': '66c53832ba1cdfc493b74f73', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:54:57.675Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,669a925bcac8fb05951d614b,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:31.425Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:36.051Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fart', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:38.277Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'frost', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:41.931Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:43.701Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'foil', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:47.086Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:49.416Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:51.165Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fruit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:56.865Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'feet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:41:59.646Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'foot', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:14.843Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'feet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:18.022Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:25.809Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'first', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:31.444Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '25', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:37.420Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'metal'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I ran through words in my mind until I came up with the best option', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '25'}, 'workerId': '669a925bcac8fb05951d614b', 'assignmentId': '66c537924bad878c3b4467ee', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:51:52.231Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6632d9ca7b5616ef7c758cd2,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:48.182Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:52.181Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:55.794Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:05.171Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:07.848Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'finish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:16.904Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fur', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:22.527Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fuck', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:30.959Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'first', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:34.944Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:45.682Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '6', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:28.995Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gun'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'animal'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'fruit'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I thought of the shape of the 3 words.', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '12'}, 'workerId': '6632d9ca7b5616ef7c758cd2', 'assignmentId': '66c537ee3f7703e33d78dd4b', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:52:09.816Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5f5aa9f89a3ef61b0778d49a,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:41:43.306Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '70', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:38.521Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'Hat'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Bar'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'Time'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bad'}, '10': {'HideTime': 23.898}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Not at all helpful', 'q6': 'Just thinking of lots of words', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '68'}, 'workerId': '5f5aa9f89a3ef61b0778d49a', 'assignmentId': '66c538048666700e1eaa3844', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:50:41.924Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,60ff1b9139cb969fbbbd4134,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:52.296Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '30', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:30.613Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'door'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'gun'}, '10': {'HideTime': 1.772}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'To see what specific words complete each individual word and based on that see if it also fits all of them.', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '15'}, 'workerId': '60ff1b9139cb969fbbbd4134', 'assignmentId': '66c53783134842459adb787f', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:52:28.920Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6609a35ed745fef53c0c1034,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:21.298Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:26.427Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fry', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:29.301Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:32.339Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fond', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:35.516Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fuel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:36.930Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:38.465Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:40.473Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fan', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:44.203Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'flour', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:47.469Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fart', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:55.188Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:08.479Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'frought', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:18.905Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'frail', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:21.532Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '40', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:13.821Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'cart'}, '10': {'HideTime': 20.053}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'My strategy was to imagine the words in my head and put different words in front or behind them.', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '36'}, 'workerId': '6609a35ed745fef53c0c1034', 'assignmentId': '66c537940b1085f744d152e7', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:52:33.770Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,581fce42429ef50001ac4fc1,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:42:40.638Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:45.642Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fuck', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:51.973Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'figure', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:42:55.882Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:01.381Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:08.615Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'frown', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:13.706Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fig', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:21.036Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '15', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:38.488Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'night'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'driving'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'some'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I guess I tried to focus on one word rathar than all of them.', 'q7': 'N/A', 'sliderValue': '9'}, 'workerId': '581fce42429ef50001ac4fc1', 'assignmentId': '66c5378e023097ed28cc6486', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:52:40.668Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5c00043a6d931200019bcb9b,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:41.041Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'flute', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:02.676Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'floor', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:10.036Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'flower', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:15.076Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:20.292Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fragrance', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:34.944Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '41', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:50.114Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'black'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'below'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'space'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'black'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'thinking', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '32'}, 'workerId': '5c00043a6d931200019bcb9b', 'assignmentId': '66c5384e08a3256a6a2c1813', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:52:42.591Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5ed42960727ce23e4d2802b6,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:43.020Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fruit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:47.640Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:50.171Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'felt', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:51.623Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'finger', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:52.579Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fault', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:54.065Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'force', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:55.363Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fire', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:56.737Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fireside', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:58.287Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fortification', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:00.843Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'felicity', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:03.634Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'feeler', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:05.549Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fart', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:07.658Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'fructose', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:10.709Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'filter', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:14.145Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'fang', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:20.625Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'fangs', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:22.345Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'feels', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:33.033Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'feelers', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:35.215Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'farts', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:36.657Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 20, 'name': 'faults', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:38.103Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 21, 'name': 'forces', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:39.613Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 22, 'name': 'firesides', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:41.580Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '90', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:47:11.707Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'book'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spider'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Not at all helpful', 'q6': ""I didn't really have a strategy, I just saw the word."", 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '90'}, 'workerId': '5ed42960727ce23e4d2802b6', 'assignmentId': '66c5389dc23973f925845905', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:52:51.080Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5ecbdb76e72f9577c2ad60d6,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:14.500Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fluent', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:21.067Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'flop', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:22.454Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'flip', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:24.537Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'flit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:25.743Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:26.601Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:27.604Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fan', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:30.199Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fans', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:31.162Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'flips', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:33.203Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'flipped', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:34.546Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'flap', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:35.887Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'flaps', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:37.106Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'flapped', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:41.420Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'filament', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:45.300Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'fill', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:47.425Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'fills', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:48.913Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'filled', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:50.317Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'fillet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:01.803Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'filleted', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:03.915Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'fillets', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:06.153Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 20, 'name': 'fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:10.824Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 21, 'name': 'fast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:12.108Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '70', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:47:43.494Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'black'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'space'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'none', 'q7': 'no r key on my keyboard and couldnt paste into the boxes so had to think of answers with no letter r in them', 'sliderValue': '61'}, 'workerId': '5ecbdb76e72f9577c2ad60d6', 'assignmentId': '66c538bb98dc076343dcfa76', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:53:09.760Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6115e6f3c50b7ffddb83a235,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:33.577Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fire', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:41.211Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:46.962Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'feline', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:50.313Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fur', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:53.447Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'freak', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:58.551Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'frond', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:01.685Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fern', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:04.307Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fungus', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:08.587Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'flax', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:12.075Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'flat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:15.240Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'flipper', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:19.403Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'frail', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:23.000Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'flail', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:25.897Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'for', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:30.149Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '58', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:47:57.485Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Blue'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'short'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spider'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'it just occurred to me', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '54'}, 'workerId': '6115e6f3c50b7ffddb83a235', 'assignmentId': '66c538ca469bd91bcf9da0ed', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:53:08.334Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66b5994895654acfd1dcbebf,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:57.766Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:10.022Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Found', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:11.189Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Figet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:17.086Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Flame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:19.125Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:20.525Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Fast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:22.961Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Facet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:25.037Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:53.307Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Flammable', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:39.905Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:46.984Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '40', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:55.548Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'stream'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Homunculus'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Echolocation'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Infinity'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'My strategy for coming up with associated word for the last three objects was to think about what each word means, envision a situation involving each word, and what I might think in each of those situations about abstraction in nature, all in order to single all one word that might capture that abstraction.', 'q7': 'None.', 'sliderValue': '40'}, 'workerId': '66b5994895654acfd1dcbebf', 'assignmentId': '66c537eb9036d73458ad591f', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:53:30.161Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,663cfbadf4198acc133f986c,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:47.855Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:50.725Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:52.149Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'false', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:53.351Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:54.504Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'frown', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:56.210Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'finnicky', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:58.361Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:59.464Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fool', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:00.719Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'found', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:02.122Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fits', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:04.669Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fester', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:07.017Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'foot', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:08.963Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'father', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:12.956Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:14.969Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'fell', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:20.350Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:22.006Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'folly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:23.245Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'feather', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:26.551Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'football', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:28.333Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'finch', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:32.785Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 20, 'name': 'fraud', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:36.354Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 21, 'name': 'fast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:39.081Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 22, 'name': 'face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:41.112Z'}, {'id': 23, 'iid': 23, 'name': 'favor', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:44.511Z'}, {'id': 24, 'iid': 24, 'name': 'flaw', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:47.070Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '50', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:02.126Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Space'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'long'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'heart'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Not at all helpful', 'q6': 'Try to find phrases that aligned ', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '50'}, 'workerId': '663cfbadf4198acc133f986c', 'assignmentId': '66c5388217d8c2ccd6870ab3', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:53:39.805Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66315c9e47e364728e8a838c,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:47:12.189Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Funny', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:18.098Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fan', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:19.356Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:20.472Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Finger', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:25.062Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:28.442Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Friendly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:29.871Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Father', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:31.049Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Feather', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:32.857Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Flow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:38.542Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Fendi', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:46.405Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Flat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:50.789Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'Forward', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:52.057Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'Face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:56.672Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'Fling', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:02.298Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'Flan', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:06.875Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'Form', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:11.152Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '44', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:49:12.115Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'first'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'marks'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'black'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'water'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'Just trying to recall stuff.', 'q7': 'None.', 'sliderValue': '53'}, 'workerId': '66315c9e47e364728e8a838c', 'assignmentId': '66c538b0269c33ccf4da085c', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:53:49.998Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5ace82e135eccf0001a11c96,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:44:47.638Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'french', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:02.128Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'foolish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:07.982Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fret', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:13.128Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:17.930Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'finger', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:23.004Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'floss', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:26.946Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'finance', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:31.900Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'for', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:33.838Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'four', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:35.397Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fail', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:38.759Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'flair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:41.857Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'funny', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:45:43.932Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '65', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:47:29.233Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'cat'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'chocolate'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'navy'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'piece'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Not at all helpful', 'q6': 'I just tried to think of a word that would fit all three words.  ', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '65'}, 'workerId': '5ace82e135eccf0001a11c96', 'assignmentId': '66c537c4269cc2a81d49917d', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:53:52.926Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,632890876b6124c7a15d06f6,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:33.911Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '35', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:37.706Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'bar'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'space'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I went through a mental list of words I associated with each and then found commonalities.', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '35'}, 'workerId': '632890876b6124c7a15d06f6', 'assignmentId': '66c538c08e87e8f8e6b89606', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:53:54.988Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6546549b0511efc35646724f,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:18.310Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:25.401Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fertilizer', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:30.441Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Farm', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:34.404Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Farming', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:38.965Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Front', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:42.508Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:45.161Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Fern', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:49.888Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:00.438Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Familiar', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:04.805Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Fennel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:11.998Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Frock', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:18.400Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '10', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:23.174Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'black'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'find words that attach to one of the three words and see if they attach to the other two and make sense', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '20'}, 'workerId': '6546549b0511efc35646724f', 'assignmentId': '66c538bf671e6f57847eef2a', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:53:55.662Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,64d53156dc399a1bcd132250,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:05.008Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '55', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:31.990Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Blue'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Space'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'door'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I repeated the words until I found one that worked for all three.', 'q7': ""I couldn't figure out how to play the snake game."", 'sliderValue': '55'}, 'workerId': '64d53156dc399a1bcd132250', 'assignmentId': '66c5388690243da91268279e', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:54:01.797Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,65959bfed43a65c4d24b7445,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:34.791Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fairy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:42.729Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'feline', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:44.959Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fantastic', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:48.423Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:51.768Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'flip', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:03.768Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'frankly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:08.103Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fidelity', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:15.248Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:18.319Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'feet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:24.648Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'foot', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:26.336Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:30.552Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fool', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:33.359Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '50', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:54.719Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'saver'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'black'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': ""going thru words in my head, starting with widow, which left me very few words that would go with it.. so them moved onto bite.. in the end, i couldn't find a match."", 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '33'}, 'workerId': '65959bfed43a65c4d24b7445', 'assignmentId': '66c537f7e14979759733ed2e', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:54:00.940Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5e0e60798205265be682850e,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:56.545Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:02.072Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:07.792Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:10.662Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:13.193Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Fiber', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:16.803Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Fix', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:18.853Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Fig', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:25.474Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Fib', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:28.824Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Feed', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:34.284Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Fade', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:38.075Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Fate', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:40.555Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'Fin', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:45.045Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'Fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:54.476Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '65', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:02.472Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spider'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'shoe'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'Try to think of words that went with one of the words, than see if they matched at all with the others.', 'q7': 'No.', 'sliderValue': '65'}, 'workerId': '5e0e60798205265be682850e', 'assignmentId': '66c5389c2a64f596fe05690e', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:54:05.472Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,60650e72f3359295eb889c0f,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:59.000Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'football', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:03.946Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:06.333Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'france', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:13.768Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:16.672Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fruit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:21.180Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'feelings', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:27.522Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:32.044Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'feet', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:35.314Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'foot', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:38.298Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'felt', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:39.528Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fort', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:44.722Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'frog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:49.760Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '46', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:47:35.244Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'coat'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'trap'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'listing words', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '50'}, 'workerId': '60650e72f3359295eb889c0f', 'assignmentId': '66c5387dd61c7b572205fbd9', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:54:16.408Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66b8c306d952179ebea2f50f,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:46.944Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fore', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:56.354Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fourth', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:59.149Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Form', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:03.807Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Fiddle', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:06.713Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Frump', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:09.368Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Fire', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:12.317Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'First', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:16.515Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Fifth', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:20.784Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Frazzle', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:25.073Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Flip', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:34.253Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Frog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:38.151Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:42.335Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '18', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:06.716Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'door'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blue'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'No strategy. ', 'q7': 'No technical issues. ', 'sliderValue': '26'}, 'workerId': '66b8c306d952179ebea2f50f', 'assignmentId': '66c538d656904fad05cf6242', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:54:28.316Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,56ccc18e4fcf69000c1718aa,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:25.048Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:30.626Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:32.377Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Freedom', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:34.170Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:35.291Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Fitness', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:36.892Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Fat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:42.077Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Fatter', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:46.850Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Fatten', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:50.053Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Fattened', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:52.153Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Freely', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:54.391Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'Finder', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:56.240Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'Finding', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:57.633Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'Findings', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:59.093Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'Fits', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:02.974Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'For', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:05.190Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'Forth', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:06.406Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'Forthright', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:09.043Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'Forethought', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:15.500Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'Fad', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:21.635Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 20, 'name': 'Fades', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:23.308Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 21, 'name': 'Fads', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:24.580Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '80', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:18.776Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'door'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blood'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'coat'}, '10': {'HideTime': 178.82399999999998}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'Just try to think of a compound word for one of the words, then see if it worked with a different word.', 'q7': ""No? Unsure. Arrows and spacebar didn't work on the snake game."", 'sliderValue': '80'}, 'workerId': '56ccc18e4fcf69000c1718aa', 'assignmentId': '66c538075e1ae61c861952e4', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:54:43.569Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5f0cc2ab16b21216d946574c,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:37.708Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:44.195Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:47.259Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fare', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:49.223Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fool', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:51.963Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'follow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:54.582Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'foolish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:58.142Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fools', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:00.985Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'foodie', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:05.557Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:08.877Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'forever', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:12.028Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:15.166Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fry', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:18.081Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'fries', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:20.864Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'fryer', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:27.396Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:30.636Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'future', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:34.116Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'fund', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:37.732Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '62', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:11.807Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'door'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '10': {'HideTime': 64.899}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I started with eight and snow, then went back to basket.', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '57'}, 'workerId': '5f0cc2ab16b21216d946574c', 'assignmentId': '66c538d2e1570e3307c5a929', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:54:43.653Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,662a4a8b566905a139dc2ce1,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:47:56.034Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fluent', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:03.486Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:05.622Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fierce', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:09.982Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fumble', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:15.158Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:20.470Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fidget', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:23.222Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:28.125Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fig', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:36.766Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:39.294Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fib', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:41.669Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:47.534Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fill', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:53.614Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'full', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:55.079Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '25', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:49:46.047Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'coat'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '10': {'HideTime': 31.66}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'Just tried thinking of what could go with the middle word first.', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '30'}, 'workerId': '662a4a8b566905a139dc2ce1', 'assignmentId': '66c538edc929c5725e8aa45c', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:55:01.580Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,662a4a8b566905a139dc2ce1,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:47:56.034Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fluent', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:03.486Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:05.622Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fierce', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:09.982Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fumble', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:15.158Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:20.470Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fidget', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:23.222Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:28.125Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fig', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:36.766Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:39.294Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fib', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:41.669Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'face', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:47.534Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fill', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:53.614Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'full', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:55.079Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '25', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:49:46.047Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'coat'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '10': {'HideTime': 31.66}, '11': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'Just tried thinking of what could go with the middle word first.', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '30'}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'Just tried thinking of what could go with the middle word first.', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '30'}, 'workerId': '662a4a8b566905a139dc2ce1', 'assignmentId': '66c538edc929c5725e8aa45c', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:55:05.232Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,634656bd2603b4db42ae94e1,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:58.833Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '85', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:48.645Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'trap'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': ""It wasn't really a strategy. It was just assessing the three words and thinking of a common related word. There was no strategy other than follow the directions and try to come up with the answer."", 'q7': 'No.', 'sliderValue': '85'}, 'workerId': '634656bd2603b4db42ae94e1', 'assignmentId': '66c538e4b744f975d1b88de5', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:54:47.483Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5f6fa02d7c95ff54da636b1f,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:33.330Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '51', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:22.867Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'military'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'tire'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blood'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'book'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': ""Tried the words they offered- if they didn't work I associated a word that was close to them"", 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '49'}, 'workerId': '5f6fa02d7c95ff54da636b1f', 'assignmentId': '66c5384cf300cdb312389ee7', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:55:15.423Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5803f6f33073510001231d9e,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:56.883Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '71', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:58.942Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'sleep'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'window'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'to come up a word that connects to any of the objects and then see if the other ones also can use those words', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '65'}, 'workerId': '5803f6f33073510001231d9e', 'assignmentId': '66c53848cbd149928f94925b', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:55:20.177Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,65e763a481f580c8f0dce113,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:49:25.943Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fries', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:36.373Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:42.021Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'flag', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:50.684Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'frog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:50:03.204Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:50:15.164Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '100', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:51:44.794Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'brown'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blue'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'It came to my mind when I first layed eyes on the words.', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '100'}, 'workerId': '65e763a481f580c8f0dce113', 'assignmentId': '66c538e13aa7d223fa9cab13', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:57:00.243Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,60ccdc25fd512fd47ae6d64c,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:47:14.023Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fire', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:27.616Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fighter', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:34.846Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Force ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:41.943Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Future', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:47.434Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Flying ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:52.669Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Free ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:58.792Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Feeling ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:04.364Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Facts ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:09.134Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '47', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:49:04.107Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'Flake'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Day'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Blood'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Black'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'Tried to see what came to mind immediately ', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '25'}, 'workerId': '60ccdc25fd512fd47ae6d64c', 'assignmentId': '66c538ddc23973f925845911', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:55:34.215Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,666379d9536eb7e9c7a0eaba,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:45.339Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:57.779Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'friends', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:09.072Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fried', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:19.120Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'four', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:26.633Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'forward', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:37.775Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '100', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:45.639Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'deserts'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'door'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'account'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'jam'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'WORD ASSOCIATION', 'q7': 'NO', 'sliderValue': '100'}, 'workerId': '666379d9536eb7e9c7a0eaba', 'assignmentId': '66c538b7e1570e3307c5a924', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:55:33.628Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5ac897a6e734400001da581c,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:03.203Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Far', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:11.689Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Few', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:17.435Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fear', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:22.254Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Father', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:27.042Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Feature', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:32.235Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'feather', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:40.352Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Figure', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:46.442Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Future', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:54.190Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Fantasy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:59.438Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '70', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:22.040Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Space'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'stock'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'pin'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I picked a word that I felt had the most associated words and tried each of its words with the other objects to find one that fit all three.', 'q7': 'No.', 'sliderValue': '40'}, 'workerId': '5ac897a6e734400001da581c', 'assignmentId': '66c5386d1d176ab4440567f4', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:55:36.560Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,65076c797ee85f5947193819,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:07.326Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:11.296Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'finish ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:14.092Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'finally ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:16.372Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'finale', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:18.731Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fish ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:23.590Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:27.938Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:29.754Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fashion', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:38.741Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'foo', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:43.600Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'flip', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:48.701Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'france', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:53.106Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fraze', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:58.341Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'fetch ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:04.331Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '30', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:50:17.107Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ray'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'school'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'work'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'back'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I was thinking about every word I knew and just praying something came up', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '9'}, 'workerId': '65076c797ee85f5947193819', 'assignmentId': '66c538d73674cea2faded11e', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:56:06.173Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66757b19a08cd45425274bd3,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:43:41.000Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:46.278Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'frank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:49.368Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'flick', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:52.606Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'flame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:54.548Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'flair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:43:58.729Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'flail', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:01.817Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fail', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:04.205Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'facilitate', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:08.858Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fetch', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:14.213Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:17.045Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'flamethrower', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:24.072Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fleece', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:28.269Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'frame', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:31.135Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'freeze', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:36.414Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:44:40.291Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '47', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:45:31.920Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Spaceship'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'spidermonkey'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Bank'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Day'}, '10': {'HideTime': 72.646}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'Daydream, Day Break, Day light ', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '51'}, 'workerId': '66757b19a08cd45425274bd3', 'assignmentId': '66c53815671e6f57847eef0f', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:56:38.957Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,668ad871a1139f6fd4158d04,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:49:12.855Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'frog', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:20.534Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:24.224Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fashion', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:31.086Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'flirt', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:34.944Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'flower', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:38.609Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'firm', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:44.930Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:49.153Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fig', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:52.461Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'full', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:55.705Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:50:00.977Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fill', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:50:04.067Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:50:08.133Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'fry', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:50:12.016Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '95', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:51:09.915Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'coin'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'coat'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'case'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'frame'}, '10': {'HideTime': 3.284}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I just tried to think about words that would be an appropriate fit.', 'q7': 'No.', 'sliderValue': '95'}, 'workerId': '668ad871a1139f6fd4158d04', 'assignmentId': '66c53954269c33ccf4da0877', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:57:23.569Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6439e861eda272218b2abec6,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:59.000Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fail', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:07.586Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'follow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:10.275Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'from', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:11.833Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fortitude', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:16.477Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fallacy', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:23.930Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:25.914Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'font', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:29.843Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'fountain', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:33.356Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'formal', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:36.423Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'frost', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:42.565Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'frostbite', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:46.743Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'frill', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:53.173Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '60', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:50:46.644Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'blood'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Band'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Gold'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I tried any word that fit with the first word and tried it with the next two.', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '50'}, 'workerId': '6439e861eda272218b2abec6', 'assignmentId': '66c53893579e4ab713b3f00b', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:57:47.087Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5f2732c17f64f043dd83bdbb,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:05.353Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fan', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:11.571Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fare', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:15.285Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fair', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:16.892Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'feast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:18.587Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:20.338Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'flat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:25.346Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'found', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:29.217Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:30.294Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'flare', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:42.182Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'felt', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:56.105Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'flake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:03.622Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '60', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:50:41.191Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'long'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'day'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blue'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'air'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I tried to think of a word that could be related to all three words.', 'q7': 'No issues', 'sliderValue': '58'}, 'workerId': '5f2732c17f64f043dd83bdbb', 'assignmentId': '66c5389d3aa7d223fa9caaff', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T00:57:58.424Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66b17a99b67f368116866c88,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:51:30.401Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'foul', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:35.527Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:36.883Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'foreever', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:40.816Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:44.841Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fabulous', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:48.552Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'forge', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:52.633Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fantastic', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:52:02.333Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'feeble', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:52:06.718Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'fast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:52:10.509Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'frenetic', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:52:17.595Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fit', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:52:25.720Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'food', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:52:28.491Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '60', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:53:43.896Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'coat'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'navy'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'The strategy for the practice rounds did not work.  I usually play Connections on NYT Games and can do these easily.  Maybe I was not thinking out of the box on this one.', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '61'}, 'workerId': '66b17a99b67f368116866c88', 'assignmentId': '66c53852dea13fa09f790ba5', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T01:00:10.344Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,667ac74b326f8ab38d0cb18d,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:50:39.584Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': ' Full', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:20.029Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:24.955Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fast', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:29.268Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'former', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:33.688Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'fury', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:37.505Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '56', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:53:29.360Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Blood'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Short'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'spider', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Super'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Log'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'Putting words with the listed three', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '57'}, 'workerId': '667ac74b326f8ab38d0cb18d', 'assignmentId': '66c538d70b1085f744d15317', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T01:00:11.815Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,667da24a3c9c2144a2c19be5,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:50.148Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fun ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:04.457Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'friend', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:11.234Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fight', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:16.584Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'find', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:21.919Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'from', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:29.244Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'free', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:34.617Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'fuss', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:41.802Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'forget', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:47.436Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '58', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:51:00.746Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'big'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'black'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'big'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'low'}, '10': {'HideTime': 3.868}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'thinking of words that go togrther', 'q7': 'yes', 'sliderValue': '37'}, 'workerId': '667da24a3c9c2144a2c19be5', 'assignmentId': '66c538b49036d73458ad5941', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T01:00:25.462Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6626f18372aacd362b3a4fe2,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:01.731Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Foil', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:08.866Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:16.549Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fossil', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:24.685Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Flag', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:38.607Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Flap', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:43.007Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Figure', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:48.252Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Famish', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:48:54.173Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Fat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:49:01.086Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '48', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:51:27.316Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'band'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'Black'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'Beach'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'I was just guessing.', 'q7': 'None', 'sliderValue': '47'}, 'workerId': '6626f18372aacd362b3a4fe2', 'assignmentId': '66c538aa9e8e5f12a4db7847', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T01:00:37.257Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,6694980a250e449b57c018cc,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:55:08.862Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fine', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:12.216Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'function', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:15.969Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fall', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:16.888Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'fallen', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:19.448Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'first', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:20.864Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'flick', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:22.615Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'flat', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:23.624Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'flop', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:24.776Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'flank', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:25.912Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'flash', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:29.128Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'fear', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:31.608Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'fearsome', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:32.912Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 12, 'name': 'flippant', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:40.785Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 13, 'name': 'focus', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:49.288Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 14, 'name': 'focusing', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:51.920Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 15, 'name': 'flirt', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:53.815Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 16, 'name': 'flush', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:55:59.712Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 17, 'name': 'flushed', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:56:03.280Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 18, 'name': 'found', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:56:06.615Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 19, 'name': 'founder', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:56:08.295Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '67', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:57:01.107Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'snow', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'snow'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'blood'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bar'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'bank'}, '10': {'HideTime': 6.143}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'no strategy', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '80'}, 'workerId': '6694980a250e449b57c018cc', 'assignmentId': '66c53a7e3674cea2faded160', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T01:02:05.460Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,65b69162f92e8eb2b3c20873,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:50:20.623Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'fat flare fast firm fun faint farm family fat firm fist full ', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:51:17.706Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'absent', '4': {'How Creative?': '100', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:54:09.998Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'ball', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'ball'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'gold'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'coat', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'coat'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'long'}, '10': {'HideTime': 101.433}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': 'I try to mention the three words differently and tried attaching it with different words till i got the most perfect attachment commonly used ', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '100'}, 'workerId': '65b69162f92e8eb2b3c20873', 'assignmentId': '66c538e1662e816f00cac3ad', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T01:02:09.654Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,5cab944b41de360017e2c3db,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:46:39.953Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Fly', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:45.509Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Fig', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:48.588Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Fissure', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:52.037Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Fix', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:53.617Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'Family', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:46:57.839Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Fake', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:00.409Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'Finite', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:05.731Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'Forward', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:12.804Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'Failure', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:23.026Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'Follow', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:28.868Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'Fierce', 'time': '2024-08-21T00:47:37.271Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '50', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:48:36.549Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Bar'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Space'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Blue'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Bank'}, '10': {'HideTime': 4.692}, '11': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T00:54:21.917Z'}, '12': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bank', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Bank'}, '13': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'blood', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Blood'}, '14': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'trap', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Trap'}, '15': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'long', 'onTime': False, 'Response': 'Band'}, '16': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'Very helpful', 'q6': ""I didn't employ any specific strategy for the last task. I tried my best to come up with a satisfactory answer and just went with it "", 'q7': 'No. Thank you!', 'sliderValue': '40'}, 'workerId': '5cab944b41de360017e2c3db', 'assignmentId': '66c538b3ba1cdfc493b74f85', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T01:03:13.065Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66882270151cacf387e98f9f,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T01:01:13.942Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'four', 'time': '2024-08-21T01:01:30.472Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'false', 'time': '2024-08-21T01:01:36.390Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'fork', 'time': '2024-08-21T01:01:42.923Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'full', 'time': '2024-08-21T01:01:49.256Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'feel', 'time': '2024-08-21T01:01:59.314Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fun', 'time': '2024-08-21T01:02:09.083Z'}]}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'coach', '4': {'How Creative?': '44', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T01:04:18.806Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'gold', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'catfish'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'band', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'fastaid'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'goldmine'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'blue', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'birdman'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'imagine, and think fast ', 'q7': 'no', 'sliderValue': '33'}, 'workerId': '66882270151cacf387e98f9f', 'assignmentId': '66c537c790243da912682785', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T01:11:48.535Z'}"
66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd,66bac9434fc0890571905fd5,"{'0': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T01:33:36.374Z'}, '1': {'FluencyInput': []}, '2': {'HideTime': 0}, '3': 'generate', '4': {'How Creative?': '85', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '5': {'PageLoad': '2024-08-21T01:35:40.692Z'}, '6': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'space', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Space'}, '7': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'door', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Door'}, '8': {'Round': 'practice', 'Prompt': 'day', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Day'}, '9': {'Round': 'test', 'Prompt': 'bar', 'onTime': True, 'Response': 'Heart'}, '10': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '66bcb3acc2bf9a8a4fb322dd', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': 'Agree', 'q4': 'A little helpful', 'q6': 'Thought of other words that could come before or after.', 'q7': 'No', 'sliderValue': '85'}, 'workerId': '66bac9434fc0890571905fd5', 'assignmentId': '66c5437b891ec2c34fcf7612', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-08-21T01:41:38.310Z'}"
